A Guide to the John Warwick Daniel Papers
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series VII. Research Material
  - Civil War Material: Virginia Confederate Artillery Units 1898-1906, n.d. (Box 24)
  - Civil War Material: Virginia Confederate Cavalry 1878-1906, n.d. (Box 24)
  - Jubal Early Material: Chapter Outlines n.d. (Box 25)
  - Jubal Early Material: Introductory Chapter (Notes and Pages of a rough draft) n.d. (Box 25)
  - Jubal Early Material: Early's life in 1861 n.d. (Box 25)
  - Jubal Early Material: First Bull Run, 21 Jul 1861 n.d. (Box 25)
  - Jubal Early Material: Williamsburg, 4 May 1862 n.d. (Box 25)
  - Jubal Early Material: Malvern Hill, 2 Jul 1862 n.d. (Box 25)
  - Jubal Early Material: Cedar Run, 9 Aug 1862 n.d. (Box 25)
  - Jubal Early Material: Antietam, 17 Sep 1862 n.d. (Box 25)
  - Jubal Early Material: Fredericksburg, 13 Dec 1862 n.d. (Box 25)
  - Jubal Early Material: Winchester, 14 Jun 1863 n.d. (Box 25)
  - Jubal Early Material: Chancellorsville, 28 Apr- 6 May 1863 n.d. (Box 25)
  - Jubal Early Material: Gettysburg, 1-3 Jul 1863 n.d. (Box 25)
  - Jubal Early Material: Appraisals of General Early 1894-1906 (Box 25)
  - Jubal Early Material: Campaigns of 1864 (Wilderness, Valley); 1865 1905-1906 (Box 25)
  - Jubal Early Material: Copies of Correspondence n.d. (Box 25)
  - Jubal Early Material: General Research Notes n.d. (Box 25)
- Series VIII. Newspaper Clippings and Scrapbooks
  - Civil War Clippings: Philadelphia Times, "Annals of the War" 1879, 4 folders (Box 26)
  - Newspaper Clippings re Civil War History 1877 Aug 20 -1905 Feb 19, 7 folders (Box 27)
  - Newspaper Clippings re Civil War History 1905 Feb 21 -1910 Feb 1, 7 folders (Box 28)
  - Newspaper Clippings re Civil War n.d., 2 folders (Box 29)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Scrapbook 1 -- enclosures 1887 Aug 29 -1988 May 25, n.d. (Box 29)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Scrapbook 2 -- enclosures 1902 Jan 8 -1904 Jun 5, n.d. (Box 30)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Scrapbook 3 -- enclosures 1906 Apr 6 -Aug 26, n.d. (Box 30)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Scrapbook 4 -- enclosures 1907 May 12 -Nov 15, n.d. (Box 31)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Scrapbook 5 1868-1869, 1873 (Box 31)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Scrapbook 6 1894 May 11 (Box 31)
  - Newspaper Clippings re Race Relations 1888 Dec 31 -1890 Aug 2, n.d. (Box 31)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Miscellaneous 1829 Apr 4 -1937 Ocy 10, n.d., 4 folders (Box 32)
- Series IX. Miscellaneous and Printed Material
  - Miscellaneous: Copy of Diary of Susannah Caroline Warwick 1829 (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous: Financial Papers 1836-1906, 2 folders (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous: Speeches by individuals other than John W. Daniel 1872-1919, n.d. (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous: Notice of State Electors 1876 (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous: Envelopes 1883, n.d. (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous: Name Cards 1891 (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous: Certificate of Membership, Confederate Veterans Camp 1892 (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous: Daniel Genealogical and Personal Material 1901, n.d. (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous: Delegate's Certificates, Confederate Camp 1901 (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous: Appointment to National Monetary Commission 1908 (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous: House Plans drawn up by William Daniel, Jr. n.d. (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous: Evaluations of Daniel's Orations n.d. (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous: Writings of John W. Daniel and John W. Daniel Jr. 1865, n.d. (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous 1833-1908, n.d. (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous: Map of William Daniel's Estate n.d. (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous: Notes n.d. (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous: Report Cards of Seth Halsey, John W. Daniel, John W. Daniel Jr., and Sarah Ann Warwick 1833-1894 (Box 33)
  - Printed Material: Invitations 1866-1914 (Box 33)
  - Printed Material: Prints and Photographs ca. 1880-1933 (Box 33)
  - Printed Material: The Confederate Veteran 1893-1894 (Box 33)
  - Printed Material: General 1870-1914 (Box 33)
  - Printed Material re Daniel, n.d. (Box 33)